Hello World

I am running everything on command line.. and its so cool!.
things I learnt => 
1. how to create a new repo and link it to a local repo and initialize it, make changes, commit changes.
2. how to create direcories, files, navigate around, code .. all without touching the mouse
3. now I am trying to push these changes to the remote reposatory
4. succesfully pushed some changes made on local machine to the remote repo on github. 

its so cool :) 
